Guide to the Susan H. Douglas political Americana collection, [1783?]-1961.
Douglas, Susan H. Political Americana Collection, [1783?]-1961
- Series VIII. Pamphlets
  - IKE: The Man You Can Trust To..., ca. 1952; 2214.PA0042 (Box 58)
  - IKE is Best for Louisiana and the Nation, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0043 (Box 58)
  - It's Clear Where Eisenhower Stands, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0044 (Box 58)
  - Eisenhower: 'No' To Democrats; 'Yes" To Republicans, 1951; 2214.PA0045 (Box 58)
  - Hello, Neighbor! Republican, Independent, Democrat, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0046 (Box 58)
  - New Jersey Republicans for Eisenhower Club Memorandum, 1952; 2214.PA0047 (Box 58)
  - The Story of Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0048 (Box 95)
  - Essex County Women's Republican Club Campaign Dinner Program, 1952; 2214.PA0049 (Box 58)
  - The Scandalous Years, 1951; 2214.PA0050 (Box 58)
  - Non-Partisan Election Information, 1952; 2214.PA0051 (Box 95)
  - Here's What a Republican Congress Did For You, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0052 (Box 58)
  - Viewpoints: If Truman Had Had His Way, 1951; 2214.PA0054 (Box 58)
  - Let's Open Both Eyes And Look At The Record, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0055 (Box 58)
  - Turn the Rascals Out!, ca. 1951; 2214.PA0056 (Box 58)
  - Keep Your Eye On the Ball!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0057 (Box 58)
  - Headlines, March 15, 1952; 2214.PA0058 (Box 58)
  - Which is YOUR Candidate?, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0059 (Box 58)
  - How the American President is Elected, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0060 (Box 58)
  - Platforms of the Republican and Copperhead Parties, ca. 1868; 2214.PA0061 (Box 58)
  - The National Life, 1870; 2214.PA0062 (Box 169)
  - An Appeal to Young Men, ca. 1879; 2214.PA0063 (Box 58)
  - Speech of Hon. Glenni W. Scofield, 1880; 2214.PA0064 (Box 58)
  - The Republican Pocket Pistol: A Collection of Facts for Freemen, 1856; 2214.PA0065 (Box 169)
  - Buffalo Daily Republic Extra: Republican Nominations, ca. 1856; 2214.PA0066 (Box 169)
  - William O. Douglas: The Man. His Life. His Views, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0067 (Box 58)
  - Citizen! Jurist! Statesman!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0068 (Box 58)
  - The Fourteen Points for Democratic Victory, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0069 (Box 58)
  - Dewey in 1948: He Gets Things Done..., ca. 1948; 2214.PA0070a (Box 58)
  - Dewey in '48: He Gets Things Done, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0070b (Box 58)
  - A Pattern for Peace, Prosperity and Progress, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0071 (Box 58)
  - Dewey Gets Things Done, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0072 (Box 58)
  - Thomas E. Dewey for President: "Proved Ability and Leadership", ca. 1948; 2214.PA0073 (Box 58)
  - Taft's Analysis of the President's Policies, 1948; 2214.PA0074 (Box 58)
  - New Jersey Republican Congressional Campaign Handbook, 1950; 2214.PA0075 (Box 58)
  - As Pegler Sees It: You Could Reach Out, Touch Next President!, 1948; 2214.PA0076 (Box 58)
  - Democrats in City Plan Dewey Group, 1948; 2214.PA0077 (Box 58)
  - We Need Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0078 (Box 58)
  - Today and Tomorrow by Walter Lippman: Eisenhower, 1952; 2214.PA0079 (Box 58)
  - Where "Ike" Stands, 1951; 2214.PA0080 (Box 58)
  - They Hate Ike, 1952; 2214.PA0081 (Box 58)
  - The Franklin D. Roosevelt Collector, November, 1948; 2214.PA0082a (Box 58)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Collectors' Association Correspondence and Membership Cards, ca. 1950; 2214.PA0082b (Box 58)
  - The Franklin D. Roosevelt Collector, May 1949; 2214.PA0083 (Box 58)
  - The Franklin D. Roosevelt Collector, November 1949; 2214.PA0084 (Box 59)
  - The Franklin D. Roosevelt Collector, May 1950; 2214.PA0085 (Box 59)
  - Books, Pamphlets, Autographs and Allied Materials Relating to Franklin Delano Roosevelt and His Times, List No. 1, 1946; 2214.PA0086 (Box 59)
  - Books, Pamphlets, Autographs and Allied Material Relating to Franklin Delano Roosevelt and His Times, List No. 2, ca. 1946; 2214.PA0087 (Box 59)
  - Books, Pamphlets, Autographs and Allied Material Relating to Franklin Delano Roosevelt and His Times, List No. 3, ca. 1947; 2214.PA0088 (Box 59)
  - Books, Pamphlets, Autographs and Allied Material Relating to Franklin Delano Roosevelt and His Times, Rooseveltiana List No. 4, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0089 (Box 59)
  - Books, Pamphlets, Autographs and Allied Material Relating to Franklin Delano Roosevelt and His Times, Rooseveltiana List No. 5, ca. 1949; 2214.PA0090a (Box 59)
  - Advertisement for FDR: His Personal Letters, Early Years, 2214.PA0090b (Box 59)
  - Advertisement for FDR: His Personal Letters, Volume II, 1905-1928, 2214.PA0090c (Box 59)
  - At Last Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., Tells the Inside Story of Roosevelt and the Russians: The Yalta Conference, 1949; 2214.PA0090d (Box 59)
  - Advertisement for This I Remember, 2214.PA0090e (Box 59)
  - Advertisement for The Public Papers and Addresses of Franklin D. Roosevelt, 2214.PA0090f (Box 59)
  - Home of Franklin D. Roosevelt National Historic Site, Hyde Park, N.Y., 2214.PA0091 (Box 59)
  - The Little White House: Georgia Home of Franklin D. Roosevelt at Warm Springs, 2214.PA0092 (Box 59)
  - Address by Franklin Delano Roosevelt, President of the United States, 1944; 2214.PA0093 (Box 59)
  - The American Farmer: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, ca. 1944; 2214.PA0094 (Box 59)
  - Which Will You Choose? A Report on the Labor Record of the Democratic Administration, ca. 1944; 2214.PA0095 (Box 59)
  - Address of the Hon. Robert S. Kerr, 1944; 2214.PA0096 (Box 59)
  - The Inside Story of the Coming Election, 1944; 2214.PA0097 (Box 59)
  - "That Man" in the White House: You and Your President, 1944; 2214.PA0098 (Box 140)
  - Alphabetical Agencies Created under the Roosevelt New Deal Party, ca. 1943; 2214.PA0099 (Box 59)
  - Frankie in Wonderland, 1934; 2214.PA0100 (Box 59)
  - What Every Good American Wants To Know About Elections, ca. 1944; 2214.PA0101 (Box 59)
  - Come to Britain: American Associations With London, 2214.PA0102 (Box 59)
  - Roosevelt and Fairbanks: Reasons for Their Election, 1904; 2214.PA0104 (Box 59)
  - Why Edison is a Progressive, ca. 1912; 2214.PA0105 (Box 59)
  - Party Platforms: Progressive, Democratic, Republican In Deadly Parallel, ca. 1912; 2214.PA0106 (Box 59)
  - "Pass Prosperity Around", ca. 1912; 2214.PA0108 (Box 59)
  - Stassen for President!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0109 (Box 59)
  - Thousands Backing Stassen With Cash, 1948; 2214.PA0110 (Box 59)
  - Harold E. Stassen on Medical Problems, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0111 (Box 59)
  - Illustrated Life of General Winfield Scott, ca. 1847-1848; 2214.PA0112 (Box 169)
  - Elegant Extracts From Rebel Writers, No. 1, ca. 1868; 2214.PA0113 (Box 59)
  - Stassen's Stands on Issues, 1952; 2214.PA0114 (Box 59)
  - Goal -- A Unanimous Republican Agreement, 1952; 2214.PA0115 (Box 59)
  - Harold Stassen's Farm Policy, 1952; 2214.PA0116 (Box 59)
  - Statement of Stassen Accomplishments, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0117 (Box 59)
  - Let The People Know...Let The People Decide!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0118 (Box 59)
  - For President: Adlai E. Stevenson / The Man American Needs, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0119 (Box 59)
  - Meet the Candidates, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0120 (Box 59)
  - Adlai Stevenson, 1952; 2214.PA0121 (Box 59)
  - Extra! Extra! General Visits New Jersey!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0122 (Box 95)
  - Estes Kefauver: One Democrat who can Beat any Republican in, 1952; 2214.PA0124 (Box 95)
  - Why Estes Kefauver Will Win The Democratic Nomination!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0125 (Box 59)
  - Kefauver Volunteer Registration Form, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0126 (Box 59)
  - Address ... Recommending Gen. Andrew Jackson, of Tennessee, to the People of New Jersey, 1824; 2214.PA0127 (Box TBD)
  - Mrs. Barney's Letter to President Jackson, ca. 1829; 2214.PA0128 (Box 59)
  - Thomas Jefferson the Giant, 1948; 2214.PA0130 (Box 59)
  - The Great Impeachment Trial of Andrew Johnson, Seventeenth President of the United States, 1868; 2214.PA0131 (Box 169)
  - Andrew Johnson National Monument, Tennessee, ca. 1947; 2214.PA0132 (Box 59)
  - The Official Truth About Harding, 1920; 2214.PA0133 (Box 59)
  - 1920 Ohio Republican State Convention Program, 2214.PA0134 (Box 59)
  - Addresses of Hon. Warren G. Harding, President of the United States and Hon. Charles E. Hughes, Secretary of State, 1921; 2214.PA0135 (Box 59)
  - 1888: The Electoral College of Ohio, 2214.PA0136 (Box 59)
  - The Harrison Almanac 1841: Improved Edition, 1840; 2214.PA0137 (Box 169)
  - The Life of Major-General William Henry Harrison, 1840; 2214.PA0138 (Box 169)
  - Roxbury Democrat--Extra. Horrible Doctrines!!! Loco Focoism Unmasked!!, ca. 1840; 2214.PA0139 (Box 59)
  - Democratic Reform: Union Soldiers Removed To Make Room For Rebels, ca. 1876; 2214.PA0140 (Box 59)
  - William Randolph Hearst, ca. 1904; 2214.PA0141 (Box 59)
  - Picture Life of a Great American, ca. 1928; 2214.PA0142 (Box 59)
  - Why Progressives Should Support Hughes, ca. 1916; 2214.PA0143 (Box 59)
  - Record of Charles E. Hughes, Governor of New York, 1906-1910, 1916; 2214.PA0144 (Box 59)
  - Hughes or Wilson? The Viewpoint Of The College Man, ca. 1916; 2214.PA0145 (Box 59)
  - More! Civil Rights Double-Talk and More Goose Eggs:, 1952; 2214.PA0146 (Box 59)
  - Democratic National Convention Official Program, 1948; 2214.PA0147 (Box 140)
  - National Young Democratic Dinner, 1948; 2214.PA0148a (Box 59)
  - Letter from Roy G. Baker to Democratic Leader, 1948; 2214.PA0148b (Box 59)
  - In The Mercury's Opinion: Is Truman Honest?, 1951; 2214.PA0149 (Box 59)
  - The G.O.P. Congress that Pigeonholed Progress!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0150 (Box 59)
  - Today's Moderns: State Young Democrats' Leader Lauds Youth Division Program, 1948; 2214.PA0151 (Box 59)
  - Hotel Directory of Delegate Headquarters, Democratic National Convention, 1948; 2214.PA0152 (Box 59)
  - Missouri Delegates To The Democratic National Convention, 1948; 2214.PA0153 (Box 59)
  - Join Young Democratic Clubs of America: Sign Up Today, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0154 (Box 59)
  - Guidebook Designed for Democratic Organization in the County and Precinct, 1948; 2214.PA0155 (Box 59)
  - Greetings to the Delegates and Alternatives of the Democratic National Convention, 1948; 2214.PA0156 (Box 59)
  - All Democrats Invited, 1948; 2214.PA0157 (Box 59)
  - Delegates Handbook, 1948; 2214.PA0158 (Box 59)
  - Taft's Training for the Presidency, 1908; 2214.PA0159 (Box 59)
  - A Sketch of the Life and Public Services of General Zachary Taylor, ca. 1848; 2214.PA0160 (Box TBD)
  - Reduction of Expenditures: Speech of Hon. W. R. Morrison, of Illinois, 1876; 2214.PA0161 (Box 59)
  - A Secret Chapter of Political History, 1878; 2214.PA0162 (Box 59)
  - Before And After The Labor-Management Relations Act of 1947 Referred to as The Taft-Hartley Law, 2214.PA0163 (Box 59)
  - The Story of Bob Taft, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0164 (Box 59)
  - My Political Credo, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0165 (Box 59)
  - Senator Robert A. Taft on Farm Policy: Excerpts from the Record, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0166 (Box 59)
  - Bob Taft: Railroad Labor's Best Friend!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0167 (Box 59)
  - Truth After Four Terms Is What We Need, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0168 (Box 59)
  - Senator Robert A. Taft on Foreign Affairs: Excerpts from the Record, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0169 (Box 59)
  - Senator Robert A. Taft on National Defense: Excerpts from the Record, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0170 (Box 60)
  - What They Are Saying: A Weekly Summary of Newspaper and Magazine Comment, 1948; 2214.PA0171 (Box 60)
  - Speaking of Vote Getters!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0172 (Box 60)
  - Tributes to Thomas A. Edison, 1951; 2214.PA0173 (Box 60)
  - You Can't Top Bob Taft For Vote Getting!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0174 (Box 60)
  - Bob Taft...GOP Winner, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0175 (Box 60)
  - Women's Stake In The 1952 Election, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0176 (Box 60)
  - Here's a Picture of the 'New' Taft, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0177 (Box 60)
  - How the Taft-Hartley Law Protects You, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0178 (Box 60)
  - Taft For President, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0179 (Box 60)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Republican Voter: Vote for Taft Primary Day, Tuesday, April 15, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0180 (Box 95)
  - Public Opinion Poll: State Survey Shows Taft Leads Ike by 10%, 1952; 2214.PA0181 (Box 60)
  - Taft Committee National Headquarters Letter to Mr. & Mrs. Damon G. Douglas, 1952; 2214.PA0182a (Box 60)
  - Delegates-At-Large, State Of New Jersey, 1952; 2214.PA0182b (Box 60)
  - New Republic, March 17, 1952; 2214.PA0183 (Box 60)
  - Plain Truth, Addressed to the Independent Electors of the State of New-Jersey, 1808; 2214.PA0184 (Box TBD)
  - Another Bid for the Presidency: This Time a Vegetarian, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0185a (Box 60)
  - Letter from Symon Gould to Susan H. Douglas, 1948; 2214.PA0185b (Box 60)
  - American Library Service List of Books on Health and Vegetarianism, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0185c (Box 60)
  - Presenting a Leader, Statesman: Joseph C. O'Mahoney, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0187 (Box 60)
  - By-Laws of the Democratic Republican General Committee of the City of New York for the Year, 1854; 2214.PA0188 (Box 60)
  - Life of Gen. Frank. Pierce, Democratic Candidate For President of the United States, 1852; 2214.PA0189 (Box 60)
  - Rules of the General Committee of Democratic Republican Young Men of the City and County of New York, 1842; 2214.PA0190 (Box 60)
  - Gov. Wilson and the Farmers, 1912; 2214.PA0191 (Box 60)
  - The National Prohibitionist, September 15, 1947; 2214.PA0192 (Box 95)
  - A Sensible Platform For Which You Should Vote, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0193 (Box 60)
  - A Pioneer in Statesmanship, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0194 (Box 60)
  - The National Prohibitionist, November 15, 1947; 2214.PA0195 (Box 95)
  - You Will Decide: Is It Time To Change Horses?, ca. 1940; 2214.PA0196 (Box 60)
  - Earl Warren For President, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0197 (Box 60)
  - Work With Wallace: Canvasser's Report, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198a (Box 60)
  - Knock on any Door!: What Every Canvasser Should Know, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198b (Box 60)
  - Henry Wallace Says 'Increase Wages Out of Profits!', ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198c (Box 60)
  - Facts to Fight With for Wallace and the New Party, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198d (Box 60)
  - Out of the Same Pocket as the Company Union, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198e (Box 60)
  - I Take My Stand with Henry Wallace, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198f (Box 60)
  - Steps To Peace, by Henry A. Wallace, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198g (Box 60)
  - Campaign Material Order Blank, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198h (Box 60)
  - Independent Progressive Party of New Jersey Canvasser Letter, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0198i (Box 60)
  - We Have a Choice: War / Peace, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0199 (Box 60)
  - A Call to the Founding Convention of the Independent-Progressive Party Of New Jersey, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0200 (Box 60)
  - Jim Crow Must Go!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0201 (Box 60)
  - An Open Letter to Premier Stalin from Henry A. Wallace, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0202 (Box 95)
  - The Citizen, June-July 1948; 2214.PA0203 (Box 95)
  - Hey, She Hasn't Registered Yet!, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0204 (Box 60)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PA0205 (Box -)
  - Souvenir and Programme of the Washington Inauguration Centennial, 1889; 2214.PA0206 (Box 60)
  - Programme of the Centennial Celebration of George Washington as President of the United States, 1889; 2214.PA0207 (Box 60)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PA0208 (Box -)
  - Morristown: A Military Capital of the American Revolution, 1950; 2214.PA0209 (Box 60)
  - Inauguration Souvenir of Cleveland and Hendricks, ca. 1885; 2214.PA0210 (Box 60)
  - Official Inaugural Program, March 4, 1933; 2214.PA0211 (Box 60)
  - Lest We Forget, 1923; 2214.PA0212 (Box 60)
  - Last Message of Warren G. Harding, Late President of the United States of America, ca. 1923; 2214.PA0213 (Box 60)
  - Program, Inauguration Ceremonies, March 4, 1913; 2214.PA0214 (Box 60)
  - Inaugural Ball, January 20, 1953; 2214.PA0215 (Box 60)
  - Souvenir, Inaugural Ball, March 4th, 1889; 2214.PA0216 (Box 60)
  - Invitation to the March 4, 1909 Inauguration Ceremonies, 2214.PA0217 (Box 60)
  - Program, Inauguration Ceremonies, March 4, 1909; 2214.PA0218 (Box 60)
  - Program for Inauguration Ceremonies, March 4, 1905; 2214.PA0219 (Box 60)
  - Invitation to the InaugurationCeremonies, March 4, 1913; 2214.PA0220 (Box 60)
  - Invitation to the Commemoration Services for Calvin Coolidge, February 6, 1933; 2214.PA0221 (Box 60)
  - Inaugural 1953 Complimentary Guide Book, 2214.PA0222 (Box 60)
  - The Diplomat: Special Souvenir Inaugural Edition, February 1953; 2214.PA0223 (Box 60)
  - Presidential Inauguration: Official Program, 1953; 2214.PA0224 (Box 93)
  - Souvenir Inaugural Poem Dedicated to Dwight David Eisenhower, ca. 1953; 2214.PA0225 (Box 60)
  - American Airlines Inauguration Timetable, 1953; 2214.PA0226 (Box 60)
  - And May The Best Man Win!, 1952; 2214.PA0227 (Box 93)
  - Announcement for William McKinley Memorial Service, 1902; 2214.PA0228 (Box 60)
  - Public Exercises in Loving Memory of William McKinley, 1901; 2214.PA0229a (Box 60)
  - Union Funeral Service For His Excellency, President William McKinley, 1901; 2214.PA0229b (Box 60)
  - Program for Public Memorial Services in Commemoration of William McKinley, Troy, New York, 1901; 2214.PA0230 (Box 60)
  - Grand Army of the Republic Memorial Circular, 1901; 2214.PA0231 (Box 60)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Inaugural Ball and Reception Card Print, 1893; 2214.PA0232 (Box 60)
  - Inauguration ReceptionInvitation, March 4, 1869; 2214.PA0233 (Box 60)
  - Presidential Inauguration Card, 1901; 2214.PA0234 (Box 60)
  - Presidential Reception Invitation, October 10, 1887; 2214.PA0235 (Box 60)
  - Vote Republican!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0236 (Box 60)
  - In Memoriam. U. S. Grant, 1885; 2214.PA0237 (Box 60)
  - All Democrats Invited, 1948; 2214.PA0238 (Box 60)
  - Instructions to Central, Sub-Precinct and Rallying Committeemen, ca. 1900; 2214.PA0239a (Box TBD)
  - The Nut-Shell, 1900; 2214.PA0239b (Box TBD)
  - Bryan's Power for Doing Mischief, 1900; 2214.PA0239c (Box TBD)
  - Lincoln, 1864 -- McKinley, 1900; 2214.PA0239d (Box TBD)
  - From President McKinley's Speech of Acceptance, July 12, 1900; 2214.PA0239e (Box TBD)
  - To the Ex=Union Soldiers..., 1900; 2214.PA0239f (Box TBD)
  - What Bryan Could Do, 1900; 2214.PA0239g (Box TBD)
  - Sound Money -- Sound Business, 1900; 2214.PA0239h (Box TBD)
  - Increased Credit of American Municipalities, 1900; 2214.PA0239i (Box TBD)
  - Godt Mynt -- Goda Affärer, 1900; 2214.PA0239j (Box TBD)
  - Ignorant Foreigners: What Bryan's Manager Says, 1900; 2214.PA0239k (Box TBD)
  - Consent of the Governed, 1900; 2214.PA0239l (Box TBD)
  - Coal: A Barometer of Prosperity and of Activity to Labor, 1900; 2214.PA0239m (Box TBD)
  - With Bryan's Consent, 1900; 2214.PA0239n (Box TBD)
  - W.J. Bryan to Populists: Speech of Acceptance Delivered at Topeka, Kan., 1900; 2214.PA0239o (Box TBD)
  - First Voters' Republican League of Ohio, 1900; 2214.PA0239p (Box TBD)
  - The Life of William Henry Harrison, 1840; 2214.PA0240 (Box TBD)
  - IKE: Man Of The Hour, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0241 (Box TBD)
  - The Presidents of the United States, 1948; 2214.PA0242 (Box 61)
  - Jackson versus Biddle: The Struggle over the Second Bank of the United States, 1949; 2214.PA0243 (Box 166)
  - This Is Ike: The Picture Story Of The Man, 1952; 2214.PA0244 (Box 61)
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine: Inauguration Number, March 1897; 2214.PA0245 (Box 166)
  - Republican Campaign Text-Book, 1920; 2214.PA0246 (Box 166)
  - Peace! Progress! Prosperity!: The Democratic Text Book, 1920; 2214.PA0247 (Box 166)
  - The Campaign Text Book of the Democratic Party of the United States, 1908; 2214.PA0248 (Box 166)
  - The Campaign Text Book of the Democratic Party of the United States, 1904; 2214.PA0249 (Box 166)
  - Republican Campaign Text Book, 1900; 2214.PA0250 (Box 166)
  - The Campaign Text Book, 1880; 2214.PA0251 (Box 166)
  - Text Book of the Republican Party, 1936; 2214.PA0252 (Box 61)
  - Republican Campaign Text-Book, 1916; 2214.PA0253 (Box 166)
  - Presidents Of The United States Of America: Portraits And Biographies, 1946; 2214.PA0254 (Box 61)
  - The Campaign Text Book, 1876; 2214.PA0255 (Box 166)
  - Beautiful Portraits of the Presidents from Washington to Hoover, 1929; 2214.PA0256 (Box TBD)
  - A Prayer for Unity, 1953; 2214.PA0257 (Box 93)
  - The Presidency of the United States of America, 1927; 2214.PA0258 (Box 61)
  - George Washington Medals of 1889, 1949; 2214.PA0259 (Box 61)
  - The Harrison's Bar Letter of Gen. McClellan, ca. 1864; 2214.PA0261 (Box 61)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PA0262 (Box -)
  - The People's Choice or Mix Your Own Candidate, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0263 (Box 61)
  - The "Little White House", 2214.PA0264 (Box 61)
  - Inaugural Souvenir, 1901; 2214.PA0265 (Box 166)
  - A Brief Guide To The Museum Collections In The Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, 1947; 2214.PA0266 (Box 61)
  - Who's going to speak up for You?, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0267 (Box 61)
  - What does 1948 add up to ... ?, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0268 (Box 61)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PA0269 (Box -)
  - You! To Up It's, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0270 (Box 61)
  - Truman Scrapbook: Washington Story in Cartoons and Text, 1951; 2214.PA0271 (Box 61)
  - Republican Fact-Book, 1952; 2214.PA0272 (Box 61)
  - The Road Ahead, 1949; 2214.PA0273 (Box TBD)
  - National Democratic Campaign Book: Presidential Election, 1900; 2214.PA0274 (Box 166)
  - Inaugural Ball Invitation, 1953; 2214.PA0275a (Box 61)
  - Inaugural Ball Admission Tickets, 1953; 2214.PA0275b (Box 61)
  - Inaugural Ball Committee Envelope, ca. 1953; 2214.PA0275c (Box 61)
  - Princeton Club of Philadelphia Reception Invitation, ca. 1914; 2214.PA0276 (Box 61)
  - Program for Memorial Services for James Abraham Garfield, 1881; 2214.PA0277 (Box 61)
  - Republican National Convention Assistant Sergeant-at-Arms Certificate, 1900; 2214.PA0278 (Box 61)
  - McKinley Day Program, 1948; 2214.PA0279 (Box 61)
  - Society of the Army of the Cumberland Reunion Invitation, 1887; 2214.PA0280 (Box 61)
  - Official Flags and Decorations, ca. 1932; 2214.PA0281 (Box 61)
  - The Facts: The Eisenhower Record vs. What Trumancrats Say, 1954; 2214.PA0282 (Box 61)
  - The Will of Mary Washington, 2214.PA0283 (Box 61)
  - Presidential Reception Invitation, 1912; 2214.PA0284 (Box 61)
  - New Jersey Republican State Committee Inaugural Dinner Invitations and Envelope, 1953; 2214.PA0285a (Box 61)
  - Reception Invitation and Envelope, 1953; 2214.PA0285b (Box 61)
  - Nixon-Case Reception Invitation and Badge, ca. 1954; 2214.PA0286 (Box 61)
  - Lincoln-Johnson Inaugural Ball Invitation, 1865; 2214.PA0287 (Box TBD)
  - Erie County Republican Banner, June 21, 1948; 2214.PA0288 (Box 95)
  - On The March With Landon and Knox, 1936; 2214.PA0289 (Box 61)
  - The Harriman Express, July 20, 1952; 2214.PA0290 (Box 95)
  - This Enemy of Negroes ... Could be YOUR Next President, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0291 (Box 95)
  - The People of New York State Back Ike!, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0292 (Box 95)
  - The Ike Shop Wholesale Price List, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0293 (Box 61)
  - The PTC Traveler: Welcome Republicans!, 1948; 2214.PA0294 (Box 61)
  - Make The Dewey Headquarters Your Headquarters, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0295 (Box 61)
  - The President, 1921; 2214.PA0296 (Box 61)
  - Warren G. Harding Funeral Admission Ticket, 1923; 2214.PA0297a (Box 61)
  - Warren G. Harding Funeral Automobile Pass, 1923; 2214.PA0297b (Box 61)
  - Warren G. Harding Funeral Poem, ca. 1923; 2214.PA0297c (Box 61)
  - Warren G. Harding Funeral Invitation Envelope, ca. 1923; 2214.PA0297d (Box 61)
  - Souvenir of our President's Visit to North Adams, June 26, 1899; 2214.PA0298a (Box 61)
  - Admission Ticket for June 26, 1899 Reception for William McKinley, 2214.PA0298b (Box 61)
  - Arlington Park Jockey Club Invitation and Envelope, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0299a (Box 61)
  - Arlington Park Jockey Club Guest Badge and Admission Tickets, 1952; 2214.PA0299b (Box 61)
  - For Your Convention Notes, 1952; 2214.PA0299c (Box 61)
  - "And I Promise!", ca. 1952; 2214.PA0299d (Box 61)
  - Letter from Abraham Lincoln to Mrs. Bixby, 2214.PA0300 (Box 95)